<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Steve Black</title>
	<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com</link>
	<description>Solo, Acoustic Singer/Songwriter</description>
	<copyright>2009 Steve Black. All rights reserved.</copyright>
	<language>en-us</language>
	
	<item>
		<title>07-23-11</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Check out this video &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-J-m8RfKqM&amp;feature=player_embedded"&gt;Steve performing at Torches on the Hudson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>09-24-10</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Check out Steve's interview with the &lt;a href="http://www.recordonline.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=%2F20100924%2FENTERTAIN%2F9240355%2F-1%2FENTERTAIN08"&gt;Times Herald Record&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>04-12-10</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Check out the first, official &lt;a href="http://www.getpersonas.com/en-US/persona/181161"&gt;steveblackonline persona&lt;/a&gt;! Wear it to show your support. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>11-23-09</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;New &lt;a href="http://www.steveblackonline.com/?i=4&amp;h=560"&gt;Discography&lt;/a&gt; page has been added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can download music and view album art. Give it a whirl...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>11-11-09</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;The new site is up with it's minimalist design. But no worries, there's more to come!&lt;/p&gt;		&lt;p&gt;Take a look around and don't forget to subscribe to the mailing list and &lt;a href="http://www.steveblackonline.com/rss/shows.xml"&gt;shows&lt;/a&gt; feed...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>04-27-07</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday marked quite an astounding event that went over . . . what's the word? . . . Oh yeah, PERFECT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last night's performance with &lt;em&gt;Justin and the Mid-Life Crisis&lt;/em&gt; was a huge success! Bobby-Q's was packed with spectators and the band was kicking it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The star of the show, our 9 year old, drumming prodigy, was spot on with some solid backing from myself, his father, Rob, and our good friend James from &lt;a href="http://www.mixopolis.com" target="_blank"&gt;Mixopolis Recording Studio&lt;/a&gt;. It was an hour or so performance, jam packed with good, old fashioned FUN.  The band was well received and Justin was simply stellar!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boys, if you're reading, well done fellas. Well done, indeed!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>03-01-04</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Tune into 101.5 WPDH radio on March 12th to hear me live on the air!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I will be performing during the Friday morning Karlson and McKenzie show, with guest DJ, 'Billy the Biker'. The show starts at 8:30am, so set your alarm clocks and make sure that you catch the show!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>02-01-04</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;My debut album, &lt;em&gt;Hello, Goodbye&lt;/em&gt;, is finished and available for purchase. The album is fully loaded with 12 original songs, all full band, consisting of catchy hooks, lush harmonies, kick-ass guitars, and power driven rhythms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The album is sure to satisfy anyone who hears it . . . in other words - there's a little something for everyone.  Make sure you check out some clips of the songs on &lt;em&gt;Hello, Goodbye&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>12-01-03</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;This is it!! I have completed the recording process for my debut album, &lt;em&gt;Hello, Goodbye&lt;/em&gt;.  The album is now in its post production phase. So, continue to check back at the website for any further details and updates!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm very excited and would like to thank everyone for being so patient and understanding during these chaotic times. Just wait a little longer! I promise that it will be well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>09-23-03</title>
		<link>http://www.steveblackonline.com/</link>
		<description>&lt;p&gt;Last night's show, opening for Duncan Sheik at Marist, was a huge success!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The venue was sold out, and the crowd responded extremely well to my music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duncan was pleasant as always and his music was entrancing. This has most definitely been a landmark moment for my career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd like to thank Bob, Sarah, everyone at student activities, and most importantly, Duncan, for one of the greatest days of my life. Cheers. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
	</item>
</channel>

</rss>